let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "1. Which of the following data type stores longest decimal number ?",
    answer: "Double",
    options: [
      "Long",
      "Float",
      "Double",
      "Short"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "2. Which of these values can be assigned to a boolean variable in Java?",
    answer: "true or false",
    options: [
      "0 or 1",
      "Any integer value.",
      "true or false",
      "Both options a and c"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: " 3. Which of these is a valid variable name?",
    answer: "var1",
    options: [
      "1var",
      "var1",
      "var@1",
      "2_var"
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 4,
    question: "4.Range of byte data type is ?",
    answer: "-128 to 127",
    options: [
      "-128 to 255",
      "-128 to 256",
      "-128 to 127",
      "-127 to 128",
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "5. Short data type has a minimum value of",
      answer: "-32,768",
      options: [
        "-2,147,483,648",
        "-32,768",
        "-32,767",
        "-127"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "6. Let a and b are the two integers. Which option can be used to check out of two numbers one is positive and the other is negative",
    answer: "a*b<0",
    options: [
      "a<0&&b>0",
      "a>0&&b<0",
      "a<0||b<0",
      "a*b<0",
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "7.What is the return type of charAt() function in String class?",
  answer: "char",
  options: [
    "int",
    "char",
    "void",
    "float"
]
},
{
  numb: 8,
  question: "8.Which of the options can be used to get the size of an array?",
  answer: "arr.length",
  options: [
    "arr.size",
    "arr.length",
    "lengthof(arr)",
    "None of these"
]
},
{
  numb: 9,
  question: "9. Which among the following are non-primitive datatypes?",
  answer: "Scanner",
  options: [
    "Array",
    "int",
    "char",
    "Scanner"
]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "10. How can we declare a 2d array with 4 rows but the number of columns in each row are not set?",
  answer: "int a []=new int [4] [];",
  options: [ 
    "int a[][]=new int [4][];",
    "int a[]=new int[4][];",
    "int a[][]=new int[4];",
    "int a[][]=new int [][4];"
]
},

];